Do you know
We are the young ghosts?
In reverse
Our stories unfold
Moving slow
We're just killing time
And we know
This fear is a crime
Surrender to your love
Surrender to your heart
Surrender
We are swimmers
Caught in the tide
Pitch black river
Shadows and light
Into the night
Beautiful swimmers
Losing the fight
A constant river
Shadows and light
Into the night
Coming home
We're shaking the grass
All alone
So far from the path
Do you know
I see you so clear?
Yes, I know
It's happening here
Surrender to your love
Surrender to your heart
Surrender
We are swimmers
Caught in the tide
Pitch black river
Shadows and light
Into the night
Beautiful swimmers
Losing the fight
A constant river
Shadows and light
Into the night
We are swimmers
Caught in the tide
Pitch black river
Shadows and light
Into the night
Beautiful swimmers
Losing the fight
A constant river
Shadows and light
Into the night